tunegenie.com 2019-10-03

# Privacy Policy

##  Overview 

This Privacy Policy applies to all of your use of any MusicToGo, LLC ("TUNEGENIE") services including information sites and services (collectively, the 'Site'). It describes how your personal information will be treated as you use our Site and services. 

We use the information we collect about you to enable social music/sharing actvities and we may, from time to time, collect information made available from the Facebook Connect program to help provide a better user experience for you as well as to market our Site to advertisers and/or potential business partners. We may use demographic information and information about the music purchases, likes, content viewed, shared, or interacted with for our purposes or to provide to business partners of TUNEGENIE. 

**BY USING TUNE GENIE SERVICES YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. PLEASE READ IT.**

##  Registering and Setting Privacy Settings 

We use the Facebook connect system. To be logged into TUNEGENIE, you must first be logged into Face book, which you can do from the TUNEGENIE site. During your initial login you will be presented with a Facebook permissions request. It will list the current requests for permissions from TUNEGENIE via Facebook and describes each permission. Below is an example of the permission request: 

You may change these individual settings at anytime by logging into your Facebook account. Click on "account", then click "applications setting", then choose TUNEGENIE which is listed with this icon and described as â€˜MUSIC PLAYLISTS" (see example below) 

##  Information We Collect and How We Use It 

When and if you subscribe to services like newsletters, alerts, special invitations or promotions or download certain software or plug-ins that may be made available by us through our Site, we may use your e-mail address or other contact information to send the information that you requested. 

When you participate in a promotional feature, we may ask for your name, home or work address, telephone number and e-mail address so we can administer the promotion. We may share this information with business partners of ours participating in or supporting the promotion. 

When you click on a banner advertisement or other link on our Site, you pass through our web server before arriving at your destination website. We track click-throughs to help us determine your interest in particular topics, measure the effectiveness of our customer communications, and to help market our Site to advertisers or potential business partners. 

We may personalize your experience by using your site behavior to shape any recommendations we may make about music files, CDs, videos and other merchandise or content (including advertising) that might be of interest to you. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and Site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the Site. 

We use "cookies" and other tracking technologies for the purposes described above as well as to enhance the functionality of the Site. This information may be stored in files on your computer that we access. For example, when you visit our Site, we may use the information stored in a cookie to store a password so that you do not have to continually input it every time you move to a different section of a password-protected portion of our Site or use a cookie from a previous visit to facilitate your use of our Site and to track usage. 

We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to our Site, new services we provide, and special offers we think will be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please contact us, and request that we discontinue providing you with such information. 

Your Facebook profile picture and name may appear in various widgets displayed on affiliate sites. If you choose to not have your Facebook picture and name appear you can deactivate a playlist by deselecting the "share on Facebook" option when you add a song to a playlist. Likes cannot be deselected and if compatible with affiliates sites may be viewed on those affiliate sites. 

We may collect anonymous demographic information that is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, domicile, age, gender, preferences and interests. We may use this information in aggregate with affiliates, advertisers, business partners or unaffiliated third parties for the purpose of performing business services for us. We may transfer information we have about you in connection with the sale of all or part of our business. We reserve the right to disclose personal information to regulatory authorities, law enforcement agencies or as required by applicable law. 

##  Digital Measurement 

  1. Our siteâ€™s media player includes proprietary measurement software which allows users to contribute to market research from Nielsen. 

  2. Here is a link to Nielsenâ€™s Digital Measurement Privacy Policy where you can access more detailed information about the measurement software and learn about your choices with regard to Nielsensâ€™s measurement. <https://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy>

  3. On Nielsenâ€™s Digital Measurement Privacy Policy page, <https://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy> in the â€œChoicesâ€ section of the Digital Measurement Privacy Policy Page;  if you do not want to participate you can Opt-Out, or Opt back in if you choose. 

##  Security 

Our Site is not designed to store sensitive personal information such as financial, health or educational records and you should not use our site for that purpose. TUNEGENIE uses measures that we believe are commercially reasonable to secure your personal information, but we cannot and do not assure that these measures will be sufficient to protect against all efforts to gain unauthorized access to the information. 

##  Third Party Sites and Services 

When you visit our Site, you may be directed to other sites outside our service. For example, credit card transactions are handled by a third-party, which receives your credit card number and other personal identifying information to process the transaction. If you click on a banner advertisement, you will leave our site. These third-party sites may send their own cookies to users to collect data or solicit personal information. TUNEGENIE allows third-party advertisers to display advertisements on the TUNEGENIE Site. These advertisers may place a persistent cookie on your computer, which will enable them to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. These other sites are not subject to our Privacy Policy and we are not responsible for the privacy policies of these third-party sites, or for the use of any information that these sites may collect. If you want to prevent one of these third-party companies from sending and reading cookies on your computer, you must contact each company's Web site individually and request that they cease such activity. 

##  Children's Privacy 

TUNEGENIE is committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Our site and services are not directed to children under the age of 13. TUNEGENIE does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If a user identifies him or herself as a child under the age of 13, we will not collect, store or use any personal information. If we receive personal information that we discover was provided by a child under the age of 13, we will promptly destroy such information. Schools and parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider the use of other means to provide a child-friendly, online environment. Additional information is available on the Direct Marketing Association's home page at [https://www.the-dma.org](https://www.the-dma.org/). If you would like to learn more about COPPA, visit the Federal Trade Commission home page at [https://www.ftc.gov](https://www.ftc.gov/). 

##  Use of Site from Outside the United States 

If you use the Site outside of the United States, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the transfer of such personal information to, and the collection and processing of such personal information in the United States and other countries or territories. The laws on holding personal information in the United States may vary and be less stringent than laws of your state or country. 

##  Agreement, Changes 

By using our Site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by TUNEGENIE as described above. If we decide to update our Privacy Policy, we will post these changes next to the Privacy Policy link on the front page of our Site. If there are material changes to the Privacy Policy, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Any information collected under our old Privacy Policy will be subject to the terms of our new Privacy Policy. 

Last Modified: October 24, 2014 

TUNEGENIE C/O MusicToGo, LLC   
Po Box 491 Riverside Ct 06878
